Masegie Handoyo

UI/UX Designer and Front-end Developer

masegihandoyo@gmail.com

Profile

Software Developer with 4 years of experience in building web for people, and currently learning lots of Product Design stuff and enjoying it very much.

Skills

UI/UX Designer

Beginner in UX copywriting. Experienced create user-centered designs by understanding business requirements and user feedback.

Front-end Developer

Building beautiful and reusable components with Vue. Experienced in making responsive and user friendly website

Tools

UI/UX Designer	Front-end Developer	
Figma	Vue	HTML5
Adobe Illustrator	React	CSS3
Adobe Photoshop	JavaScript	

Experience

UI/UX Designer - Seasonal, Indomaret

2021-Present

- Contributed to the redesign of many internal website, resulting in a modern and userfriendly interface.
- Meetings with users to discuss problems faced and resolve problems with business requirements and user feedback
- · Build a little design system for my team
- Create user-centered copy, wireframes, high-fidelity design, and prototypes using Figma.
- Teaching UI Fundamental, Figma (Design System, Auto Layout, Variable).

Lead FE Developer, Indomaret

2022-Present

- Collaborate with other leads and project managers to plan and estimate frontend development tasks.
- Guide and mentor junior developers, Teaching Front End Development, mostly JavaScript.

Full-Stack Developer, Indomaret

2020-2021

- Collaborate with other leads and project managers to plan and estimate frontend development tasks.
- Guide and mentor junior developers, Teaching Front End Development, mostly JavaScript.

FE Developer, Indomaret

2019-2020

- Collaborate with other leads and project managers to plan and estimate frontend development tasks.
- Guide and mentor junior developers, Teaching Front End Development, mostly JavaScript.

Education

Universitas Atma Jaya Yogyakarta